<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>italian &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/italian/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>italian &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Italio</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/06/this-is-italio-kitchen-which-has-recently-opened/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 19:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Italio Kitchen]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/06/this-is-italio-kitchen-which-has-recently-opened/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>This is Italio Kitchen which has recently opened in Winter Park. Think of it as the Chipotle of Italian food. When you enter you pick your pasta (wheat or flour), your meat (sausage, chicken, beef, or veggie), your sauce (alfredo, tomato, or a few different kinds of pesto), and then all of your toppings. As [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/06/this-is-italio-kitchen-which-has-recently-opened/">Italio</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/06/this-is-italio-kitchen-which-has-recently-opened/attachment/200/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/tumblr_mnqaoyAwzU1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>This is <a href="http://italiokitchen.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Italio Kitchen</a> which has recently opened in Winter Park. Think of it as the Chipotle of Italian food.</p>
<p>When you enter you pick your pasta (wheat or flour), your meat (sausage, chicken, beef, or veggie), your sauce (alfredo, tomato, or a few different kinds of pesto), and then all of your toppings. As you work your way down the line the bowl gets more and more full and then you pay and eat.</p>
<p>I tried the flour pasta with sausage, alfredo and tomato sauces, and added in red peppers, a brushetta mix, and topped with shaved parmesan. It was really good. And for the price (about $7), it was a ton of food and quite a good value.</p>
<p>I think Italio can do well as there really isn’t a fast-casual Italian place here in Orlando. It is a chain, but a local one that seems to have it’s ducks in a row. I can see these popping up all over the place.</p>
<p>Visit <a href="http://italiokitchen.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Italio Kitchen</a> on South Orlando in Winter Park.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/06/this-is-italio-kitchen-which-has-recently-opened/">Italio</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mangia Mobile</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/11/the-mangia-mobile-is-a-new-food-truck-in-town/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 21:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[food trucks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mangia Mobile]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/11/the-mangia-mobile-is-a-new-food-truck-in-town/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Mangia Mobile is a new food truck in town serving up Italian favorites. I’m a sucker for good, creamy pasta so this was a no brainer for me. This is the Pasta Ashley: a chicken, alfredo sauce, and sun dried tomatoes combination on top of fettuccine. It was really good. The sauce was great. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/11/the-mangia-mobile-is-a-new-food-truck-in-town/">The Mangia Mobile</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/11/the-mangia-mobile-is-a-new-food-truck-in-town/attachment/309/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/tumblr_mdjfjqCqHm1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>The Mangia Mobile is a new food truck in town serving up Italian favorites. I’m a sucker for good, creamy pasta so this was a no brainer for me.</p>
<p>This is the Pasta Ashley: a chicken, alfredo sauce, and sun dried tomatoes combination on top of fettuccine. It was really good. The sauce was great. I would have preferred a bit more sun dried tomatoes, but that might just be me. It was a really good dish and something unique from a food truck here in town.</p>
<p>You can follow the <a href="http://twitter.com/themangiamobile" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mangia Mobile</a> on Twitter.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/11/the-mangia-mobile-is-a-new-food-truck-in-town/">The Mangia Mobile</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lido&#8217;s Italian</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 18:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido's]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>I must drive by Lido’s Italian half a dozen times a week. It’s located right at Orange and Michigan next to Play it Again Sports, and if you weren’t looking for it you’d never know it was there. But Lido’s is an Orlando staple and has seemingly been where it is forever. We went for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/">Lido&#8217;s Italian</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/attachment/435/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m5b1gwPNxn1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/attachment/436/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m5b1gwPNxn1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>I must drive by Lido’s Italian half a dozen times a week. It’s located right at Orange and Michigan next to Play it Again Sports, and if you weren’t looking for it you’d never know it was there. But Lido’s is an Orlando staple and has seemingly been where it is forever.</p>
<p>We went for dinner and the dining room was small, but filled with what seem to be regulars. An older couple a table over even ordered “the usual, but with meatballs.” I can see why people come back. The wait staff is friendly, more in line with your neighborhood diner, are address you as “deer.” This is a trait lost on a lot of waitresses these days.</p>
<p>The menu is simple – it’s your basic Italian menu but one block in the center of the menu caught my eye. The Pizzaoli is a unique dish that is listed as Lido’s best seller so I figured I’d give it a shot. It’s two chicken cutlets (unless you get the “large” plate which is three) with a layer of roasted red peppers, another layer of mozzarella, a pepperoni or two, and Lido’s marinara sauce served with a side of angel hair. The dish is delicious. All those flavors work really well together, and the roasted red peppers were a wonderful surprise on my first bite.</p>
<p>Carla ordered the tri-colored tortellini in a “pink” Alfredo sauce and asked to add mushrooms. The plate that arrived could have fed both of us, it was so large. The sauce was absolutely amazing and surprisingly thick. Needless to say, a box was definitely requested.</p>
<p>Lido’s also adds endless salad and breadsticks, a la Olive Garden, to their entrees. But unlike Olive Garden, their salad dressing tastes fresh and homemade, the croutons are obviously yesterdays breadsticks (which is awesome), and the breadsticks are giant, twisted monsters that just beg to be dipped in the sauce of whatever is on your plate.</p>
<p>Overall, Lido’s was a wonderful surprise. It’s not fancy, it’s not over complicated, but it’s good food with friendly service. Don’t waste your time looking for a website, because you won’t find one. But next time your on Michigan, right at the corner with Orange, take a look and you’ll see it. It’s next to Play it Again Sports and directly across the street from Arby’s. Parking is in the rear.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/">Lido&#8217;s Italian</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buca di Beppo</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/buca-di-beppo/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 19:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buca di Beppo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/buca-di-beppo/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The other day some good friends of ours got married (congratulations you guys!) and we were invited to their rehearsal dinner at Buca di Beppo in Maitland. We had no idea we were going to be in for such a treat. After what we learned was the appetizer was served, we found out that this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/buca-di-beppo/">Buca di Beppo</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The other day some good friends of ours got married (congratulations you guys!) and we were invited to their rehearsal dinner at Buca di Beppo in Maitland. We had no idea we were going to be in for such a treat. After what we learned was the appetizer was served, we found out that this meal would span five glorious courses over about two solid hours. Since we didn&rsquo;t want to be rude and take pictures of our food in the middle of a rehearsal dinner, you&rsquo;ll have to deal with our descriptions.</p>
<p><strong>First Course &#8211; Antipasti and Pizza<br /></strong>The night began with a nice caprese salad: nice and ripe tomato slices with thick, fresh mozzarella drizzled with some olive oil. Nice and light and a great way to start. Paired with the caprese was a Margherita pizza &ndash; basically the exact same thing but in pizza form. Also very good.</p>
<p><strong>Second Course &#8211; Salad<br /></strong>We had a Caesar and a mixed green salad. What can you really say about salad?</p>
<p><strong>Third Course &#8211; Pasta<br /></strong>This course brought two amazing options: Penne Basilica and Ravioli al Pomodoro. The penne, covered with chopped broccoli and a cream sauce, was very rich and very good. However the ravioli stole the show. The massive mixture of cheeses (listed on the website as mozzarella, provolone, ricotta, and parmesan) make each bite nice and rich and very delicious. This might have been my favorite dish of the night.</p>
<p><strong>Fourth Course &#8211; Entrée<br /></strong>For the main course, we had both chicken and eggplant parmesan as well as green beans and broccoli. The chicken parm was delicious; crispy with a nice bite from the sauce and richness from the cheese. The eggplant parm was basically the exact same thing, just with eggplant instead of chicken. The only thing we wished was that the eggplant was cut a little thicker. The green beans were nice, although a little oily and the broccoli was dusted with parmesan cheese and cooked in garlic. They were pretty good.</p>
<p><strong>Fifth Course &#8211; Dessert<br /></strong>By the time dessert was served, we were almost fully in our food comas. However when the &ldquo;Double Dark Chocolate Cake&rdquo; arrived, our interest was re-piqued. Rich, but not too rich, the chocolate cake was very good. The cake was served with a giant (and when I say giant I mean seriously huge) bowl of tiramisu. I&rsquo;m not a huge coffee fan, but I figured I had tried everything else on the table thus far so I might as well try the tiramisu as well. It was good, and not too espresso-like, but after the giant slice of cake I only managed a few bites of tiramisu.</p>
<p>Since everything at Buca di Beppo is served family style, our table ended up with a lot of left overs. A whole lot of left overs. Enough, in fact, to produce two more full meals at home. And I&rsquo;m eating the final piece of chocolate cake once I finish writing this post. Everything about our Buca di Beppo was wonderful. And since it was the rehearsal dinner for our friend&rsquo;s wedding, it was even more special.</p>
<p>Buca di Beppo is in Maitland on 17-92 right across from the Enzian Theater.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/buca-di-beppo/">Buca di Beppo</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shine Neighborhood Kitchen</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/last-night-we-went-out-to-dinner-for-justins/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shine Neighborhood Kitchen]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/last-night-we-went-out-to-dinner-for-justins/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Last night we went out to dinner for Justin’s birthday to a wonderfully hidden restaurant called Shine Neighborhood Kitchen appropriately located on Shine Ave. I get to be the one posting about it because I definitely out ordered him when it came to this meal, sorry sweetie. In the picture is my wonderful fruitti with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/last-night-we-went-out-to-dinner-for-justins/">Shine Neighborhood Kitchen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/last-night-we-went-out-to-dinner-for-justins/attachment/674/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/tumblr_lro7m7TPqV1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>Last night we went out to dinner for Justin’s birthday to a wonderfully hidden restaurant called Shine Neighborhood Kitchen appropriately located on Shine Ave. I get to be the one posting about it because I definitely out ordered him when it came to this meal, sorry sweetie. In the picture is my wonderful fruitti with muscles, shrimp, and snapper served over a bed on linguini. The wonderful surprise for me was the delicious sauce that it is swimming in. This tomato sauce is more like a broth and has a surprising bite to it which was a fantastic little secret that wasn’t mentioned on the menu.</p>
<p>As an appetizer we had the calamari which, in my opinion, was perfectly breaded and had the perfect amount of sea salt to make you want more and more. If you have not had the pleasure of visiting Shine, that might I suggest planning to go there on your next date night.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/last-night-we-went-out-to-dinner-for-justins/">Shine Neighborhood Kitchen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
