<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tacos el Rancho &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/tacos-el-rancho/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Tacos el Rancho &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tacos el Rancho</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/a-few-weeks-ago-anonymous-suggested-we-try-tacos/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mexican]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tacos el Rancho]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/a-few-weeks-ago-anonymous-suggested-we-try-tacos/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A few weeks ago Anonymous suggested we try Tacos el Rancho at the corner of Conway and Hoffner, right next to the McDonald’s. It’s taken a little while but we finally got over there and it’s time to share the results. I’ve been to Tacos a few times in the past, though it was Carla’s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/a-few-weeks-ago-anonymous-suggested-we-try-tacos/">Tacos el Rancho</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/a-few-weeks-ago-anonymous-suggested-we-try-tacos/attachment/660/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/tumblr_ls6iy4yurQ1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/a-few-weeks-ago-anonymous-suggested-we-try-tacos/attachment/661/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/tumblr_ls6iy4yurQ1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>A few weeks ago <a href="http://chowdownorlando.com/post/9670097964/ok-so-i-thought-of-another-great-restaurant-that-is" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Anonymous suggested</a> we try Tacos el Rancho at the corner of Conway and Hoffner, right next to the McDonald’s. It’s taken a little while but we finally got over there and it’s time to share the results.</p>
<p>I’ve been to Tacos a few times in the past, though it was Carla’s first experience. The thing about Tacos is that you have to ignore the cheesy faux Mexican decor and the fact that it’s in a shopping center across from a McDonald’s. You ignore these first impressions because what you get at Tacos is really good, authentic food. Whenever you need to know at least a few words in Spanish in order to read the menu at a mexican restaurant, you know you’re in the right place.</p>
<p>I had the pastor (read marinated, cut pork) burrito and a chicken soft taco. Both had salsa, cheese, cilantro, onions, pico, and sour creme and the burrito also had black beans and rice. Both were very good. Both meats were a little over cooked, but were seasoned exceptionally.</p>
<p>Carla had pastor enchiladas with a side of rice and beans and a mango soda imported from Mexico. I don’t drink soda, but this was delicious. Nice and sweet.</p>
<p>When it comes to Mexican restaurants, for me it really comes down to the queso. I have a friend that believes if you have to pay for chips, the restaurant isn’t worth going to, and while you do have to pay for chips at Tacos el Rancho, it’s worth it to get to the queso. It’s a nice, creamy white queso that has just the right amount of heat with it’s peppers. The chips are good too, especially when you come across one that was sprinkled with lime juice.</p>
<p>Overall Tacos el Rancho is a really great Mexican restaurant here in Orlando and worth checking out if you’ve never been there.</p>
<p>Tacos el Rancho is at the corner of Conway and Hoffner right next to McDonald’s.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/a-few-weeks-ago-anonymous-suggested-we-try-tacos/">Tacos el Rancho</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
