<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Pine 22 &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/pine-22/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Pine 22 &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Pine 22</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/11/last-week-we-ate-at-pine-22-the/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 00:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burgers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pine 22]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/11/last-week-we-ate-at-pine-22-the/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Last week we ate at Pine 22, the choose-your-own-adventure burger place in The Plaza downtown. Upon entering, you are presented with a table containing a bunch of pads and golf pencils. The pad contains all the options to build your ideal burger, including type of burger, type of bread, type of cheese, sauces, and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/11/last-week-we-ate-at-pine-22-the/">Pine 22</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/11/last-week-we-ate-at-pine-22-the/attachment/629/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/tumblr_lufdgxCjRQ1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/11/last-week-we-ate-at-pine-22-the/attachment/630/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/tumblr_lufdgxCjRQ1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>Last week we ate at Pine 22, the choose-your-own-adventure burger place in The Plaza downtown. Upon entering, you are presented with a table containing a bunch of pads and golf pencils. The pad contains all the options to build your ideal burger, including type of burger, type of bread, type of cheese, sauces, and a whole slew of topping options.</p>
<p>After spending a few minutes working through the pad, the next step in the process seems absolutely pointless: you take it to another counter where the hostess rings you up – entering each option into the computer. It took just as long for her to enter the options in as it did to fill out the paper. It seems that the process could be subverted and made much more user friendly by having the servers turn into waitresses. But that might be too complicated.</p>
<p>Regardless, we paid (something you do up front, again, no waitresses, only servers) and found our own table. This is when I noticed the next strange occurrence regarding Pine 22: the place was practically empty. It was around 6p, mid-week, but still, other than us there was only one other table. But that wasn’t what was really strange, this was: a man came in about 5 minutes after us and informed one of the servers he had a small group of people meeting here shortly and was wondering if he could put some of the tables together. The server, and let me remind you the place was empty, told the man she would have to ask the manager to make sure that was ok. In the 30 minutes or so we spent in the place, we noticed that none of the staff really seemed like they wanted to be there.</p>
<p>Often times I can look the other way when service is bad as long as the food is good. Here, it’s ok. I ordered a beef burger with fontina cheese, caramelized onions, lettuce, pickles, tomato, and asked for the homemade mango chutney and homemade barbecue sauces on the side. The burger itself was good, but nothing to really write home about. The cheese was almost nonexistent. The sauces, however, were very tasty. Carla ordered a mushroom burger with feta, sun dried tomatoes and a the rest of the healthy stuff in the picture. She, on the other hand, really enjoyed her burger.</p>
<p>We also ordered a combo of onion rings and sweet potato french fries. Both were pretty much as you’d expect, not bad. They were served with a homemade herb aioli that, like the sauces with the burger, really the highlight.</p>
<p>The sad thing is that we really wanted to like this place. I mean, custom burgers? What’s not to like? But the problem is that the food doesn’t really save the fact that the concept itself is flawed. The one nice thing is that Pine 22 tires to use as many locally grown products as possible and tells you, on the receipt, which local farms you supported with your order; we supported 4.</p>
<p>Pine 22 is on Pine St in The Plaza downtown.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/11/last-week-we-ate-at-pine-22-the/">Pine 22</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
