<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Burger Fi &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/burger-fi/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Burger Fi &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Burger Fi</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/12/weve-been-hearing-a-lot-about-burger-fi-the-new/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Burger Fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burgers]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/12/weve-been-hearing-a-lot-about-burger-fi-the-new/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>We’ve been hearing a lot about Burger Fi, the new gourmet burger place open on Park Ave, all of it really good. It was only a matter of time for us to get over there and once we saw a picture a friend posted of the logo stamped Burger Fi bun, we were sold. We [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/12/weve-been-hearing-a-lot-about-burger-fi-the-new/">Burger Fi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/12/weve-been-hearing-a-lot-about-burger-fi-the-new/attachment/290/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/tumblr_meu2w7WqNA1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>We’ve been hearing a lot about <a href="http://burgerfi.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Burger Fi</a>, the new gourmet burger place open on Park Ave, all of it really good. It was only a matter of time for us to get over there and once we saw a picture a friend posted of the logo stamped Burger Fi bun, we were sold. We went the very next day.</p>
<p>When you arrive at Burger Fi on Park Ave, it seems like the perfect Park Ave place – wide open doors spilling out onto a large patio with a ton of tables, all packed with happy people. It’s a good sign. The line was long, but moved ridiculously fast leaving very little time to ponder all the burger toppings. They range from grilled onions to fried eggs, and then some. When we made it to the front of the line, our order was longer than expected because everything sounded so good and, as twitter follower Derek recommended, we went hungry.</p>
<p>We ended up ordering the breakfast burger (burger topped with bacon, eggs, hash browns, and even some maple syrup) and their namesake burger with an addition of grilled onions. On top of the burgers, we went with a basket of Urban Fries which is on the “secret menu” found on the Burger Fi website. These were recommended by friends of ours as simply to die for. They are fries topped with a Parmesan cheese and herb mixtures and covered with garlic aioli. Very good. We also got onion rings, which like Googie Burger in Atlanta, are oversized and amazing. We had also heard a lot about the Burger Fi frozen custard shakes. These are milkshakes without the milk – cream, eggs, sugar – and banana in our case. It was awesome and had straw-sized slivers of banana mixed in.</p>
<p>Overall Burger Fi is a great addition to the Park Ave offerings. The food is fantastic and, honestly, what can be better than eating outside in the sun in mid-December?</p>
<p>Head down to Burger Fi on Park Ave, you’ll be very happy you did. But, like Derek suggested, go hungry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/12/weve-been-hearing-a-lot-about-burger-fi-the-new/">Burger Fi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
