<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Spooky&#8217;s Black Cat Cafe &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/spookys-black-cat-cafe/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Spooky&#8217;s Black Cat Cafe &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Spooky&#8217;s Black Cat Cafe</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/to-be-honest-with-you-i-have-never-noticed/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 18:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spooky's Black Cat Cafe]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/to-be-honest-with-you-i-have-never-noticed/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>To be honest with you, I have never noticed Spooky’s Black Cat Cafe at the corner of Robinson and Primrose. It’s been there for over a year, and as far as I knew it was still The Sandwich King. But at the urging of my brother, we gave Spooky’s a try. Don’t let the exterior [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/to-be-honest-with-you-i-have-never-noticed/">Spooky&#8217;s Black Cat Cafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/to-be-honest-with-you-i-have-never-noticed/pulled-pork-on-waffels/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m5b2ajx31X1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/to-be-honest-with-you-i-have-never-noticed/sweet-potato-cakes/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m5b2ajx31X1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/to-be-honest-with-you-i-have-never-noticed/fungus-flatbread/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m5b2ajx31X1r1ujdyo3_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>To be honest with you, I have never noticed <a href="http://www.themilkdistrictmarketplace.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Spooky’s Black Cat Cafe</a> at the corner of Robinson and Primrose. It’s been there for over a year, and as far as I knew it was still The Sandwich King. But at the urging of my brother, we gave Spooky’s a try. Don’t let the exterior of the building scare you away, and don’t be thrown by the tremendous amount of Halloween decorations inside, sit down and prepare your palate for a wonderful ride.</p>
<p>Spooky’s is a small place – there’s one waiter, one dishwasher, and one cook. At the top of the menu is a note informing you that all dishes are cooked to order with care, to provide the freshest food possible. And they are. Don’t expect your food to come out quickly, this is a place where you sit down with friends and enjoy yourselves rather then rush in, get fed, and leave.</p>
<p>And boy is the food worth waiting for.</p>
<p>We started with the Sweet Potato Cakes (bottom left). These wonderful concoctions are super sweet and served drizzled in honey, dates, and seemingly candied prosciutto. Honestly, what’s not to love?</p>
<p>For the main meal, I was torn between a number of things. The chorizo over hominy sounded wonderful, as did the “Best Meatloaf Sub in Town,” and of course there was “The Sandwich King,” a slight tip of the hat to the locations former occupant. But one thing kept drawing my eye, and that was the Pulled Pork on Waffles (pictured at the top).</p>
<p>This dish came out and upon the first bite, all I could thing was “wow.” The pork is milk-stout braised and served with an amazing sauce on top of very sweet, crispy waffles. On the side is a chimichurri and a sweet bbq sauce, but those are only added bonuses as the main sauce is so good.</p>
<p>Pictured on the bottom right is the flatbread that Carla ordered. Note that this is the small portion and the large is almost twice that size. It had a bunch of different mushrooms, wonderful cheese and was topped with a curry sauce. I’m not a big mushroom fan, but the pizza was very good.</p>
<p>Spooky’s is such an amazing value that you’ll be surprised at the portions that arrive. The food is fantastic and completely worth the wait.</p>
<p>You can find Spooky’s Black Cat Cafe in the Milk District on N Primrose, across from 7-11.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/to-be-honest-with-you-i-have-never-noticed/">Spooky&#8217;s Black Cat Cafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
