<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>sushi &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/sushi/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>sushi &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Shin Shushi</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 21:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sushi]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A few weeks ago Carla and I were looking for a nice place to eat before going to see Les Miserables at the Bob Carr. We put the question out on Twitter and received recommendations from fellow local bloggers Droolius and Eat Local Orlando. We took Droolius’ recommendation for Shin Shushi on North Orange Ave. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/">Shin Shushi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/attachment/544/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/tumblr_ly6bv5mL8a1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/attachment/545/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/tumblr_ly6bv5mL8a1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/attachment/546/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/tumblr_ly6bv5mL8a1r1ujdyo3_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>A few weeks ago Carla and I were looking for a nice place to eat before going to see <em>Les Miserables</em> at the Bob Carr. We put the question out on Twitter and received recommendations from fellow local bloggers <a href="http://droolius.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Droolius</a> and <a href="http://www.eatlocalorlando.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Eat Local Orlando</a>. We took Droolius’ recommendation for <a href="http://www.shinsushi.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shin Shushi</a> on North Orange Ave. We’re really glad we did!</p>
<p>We started off with Beef Kushi Katsu, which were small, panko battered beef and vegetable skewers. I don’t know if I’ve ever had breaded and deep fried beef before and I’m not really sure why that is because it’s delicious.</p>
<p>Typically Carla is into sashimi and was very tempted to go in that direction. However some of the speciality rolls caught our eye and we went in a different direction for dinner. For our main course, we split three sushi rolls:</p>
<ul>
<li>The Maine (top right roll in the picture): An entire lobster roll tempura fried with some other additions. It was really good and surprisingly light for how large it was.</li>
<li>Crunch California (middle roll in the picture): This was your basic California roll, but tempura battered and deep fried. I had to try it and was very happy I did. It was good, especially when dipped in spicy mayo.</li>
<li>Surf and Turf (bottom left roll in the picture): Tempura battered strip and asparagus inside the roll with seared NY strip steak and a wasabi mayo on top. To say this was one of the best pieces of sushi I’ve ever eaten would be pretty close to the truth. And the best part was Carla didn’t like the mayo on top, so it was all mine.</li>
</ul>
<p>For dessert, we tried the tempura fried cheesecake (who wouldn’t?). It was really good. Basically two entire slices of cheesecake battered and fried (notice a patter with our choices for the evening?) served with a nice ice cream. It was a nice ending to the meal.</p>
<p>We were really happy with Droolius’ recommendation and are now passing it on: If you’re looking for really good sushi, check out Shin on North Orange Ave.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/">Shin Shushi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fish Out of Water</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/i-am-a-big-fan-of-sushi-there-is-something-about/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2011 21:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fish Out of Water]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FOOW]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[potstickers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spicy tuna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sushi]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/i-am-a-big-fan-of-sushi-there-is-something-about/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>I am a big fan of sushi. There is something about eating raw fish that seems so right and so wrong all at the same time. I have to admit, however, that I was slightly skeptical about eating sushi from a food truck (I’m not sure why since there is nothing that I have eaten [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/i-am-a-big-fan-of-sushi-there-is-something-about/">Fish Out of Water</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/i-am-a-big-fan-of-sushi-there-is-something-about/attachment/581/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/tumblr_lwo0pasdmO1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>I am a big fan of sushi. There is something about eating raw fish that seems so right and so wrong all at the same time. I have to admit, however, that I was slightly skeptical about eating sushi from a food truck (I’m not sure why since there is nothing that I have eaten that came from a truck that I didn’t like). Fish out of Water didn’t disappoint. The only sushi roll I had was the spicy tuna, and it was one of the best spicy tuna rolls I have ever eaten. The fish was perfectly seasoned and topped with delicious sauce. To fulfill my love of potstickers, I had to give them a try too. FOOW has two versions of their potstickers: veggie and pork. I went for pork and had so much fun eating them. They were cooked to perfection and were absolutely delicious. If you love sushi or just want to give it a try, some of the best sushi in town can be found on a truck, just visit Fish out of Water to satisfy all of your sushi needs.</p>
<p>You can find Fish Out of Water by <a href="http://twitter.com/fishoutofwater8" target="_blank" rel="noopener">following them on Twitter</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/i-am-a-big-fan-of-sushi-there-is-something-about/">Fish Out of Water</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bento Cafe</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 23:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sushi]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Prior to a year or so ago I did everything I could to stay away from sushi. The idea of raw fish wrapped up with rice sounded absolutely unappealing to me. Then I was introduced to the fact that most sushi isn’t actually raw. And now I’m a huge fan. The reason for my sushi [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/">Bento Cafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/attachment/608/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/tumblr_lvt6lxY9Wk1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/attachment/609/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/tumblr_lvt6lxY9Wk1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>Prior to a year or so ago I did everything I could to stay away from sushi. The idea of raw fish wrapped up with rice sounded absolutely unappealing to me. Then I was introduced to the fact that most sushi isn’t actually raw. And now I’m a huge fan.</p>
<p>The reason for my sushi conversion is Bento Cafe in Downtown Orlando. We’ve talked about Bento before, as it’s one of our favorite places to eat in all of Orlando. They have great boxes, but the other day our meal was all about the sushi.</p>
<p>On this trip I ordered my favorite roll on the menu, the Special Mexican (pictured in the foreground of the picture above). The Special Mexican is tempura shrimp, cream cheese, avocado, topped with ebi, eel sauce, and spicy mayo. The crunch from the shrimp mixed with the delicious spicy may make for a really good combination.</p>
<p>Usually I pair this with a Dragon roll, but thought to venture to the other side of the menu on this trip. The back side has all kinds of speciality rolls that, frankly, usually intimidate me. To join the Special Mexican, I added the Bali Hai Mango. This roll is also shrimp tempura, cream cheese, and eel but is instead topped with mango and coconut flakes and then drizzled with eel sauce. Where the Special Mexican has that slightly spicy, creamy flavor from the mayo, the Bali Hai has a sweet and rough texture from the mango and coconut. It was very good.</p>
<p>Also pictured is the sashimi bowl that Carla got. It’s pictured because it’s pretty, but like I said above, it’s all raw and I don’t do raw fish. She really likes it though.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.bentocafesushi.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bento Cafe</a> is located in The Plaza downtown on Orange Ave.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/">Bento Cafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
