<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Pom Pom &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/pom-pom/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Pom Pom &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tako Cheena</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/02/what-you-see-are-the-three-speciality-tacos-from/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 20:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pom Pom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tacos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tako Cheena]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/02/what-you-see-are-the-three-speciality-tacos-from/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>What you see are the three “speciality tacos” from Tako Cheena, the taco concept by Pom Pom. We’ve eaten at Tako Cheena and the verdict still remains, the Panko Crusted Cod (on the left) is probably the best taco in town. I could eat it every single day and not get tired of it. Also [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/02/what-you-see-are-the-three-speciality-tacos-from/">Tako Cheena</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/02/what-you-see-are-the-three-speciality-tacos-from/attachment/240/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/tumblr_mi2ldyWMTi1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>What you see are the three “speciality tacos” from <a href="/tagged/Tako-Cheena" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tako Cheena</a>, the taco concept by Pom Pom. We’ve eaten at Tako Cheena and the verdict still remains, the Panko Crusted Cod (on the left) is probably the best taco in town. I could eat it every single day and not get tired of it.</p>
<p>Also pictured is the Char Siu BBQ Pork taco (center) which is well seasoned and sauce covered pork that just falls apart with each bite. On the right is the Tom Mojo Shrimp taco which is also really good.</p>
<p>As we’ve said many times before, Pom Pom is one of our favorite places in town, and their taco option, Tako Cheena, is another winner.</p>
<p>You can find <a href="http://www.takocheena.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tako Cheena on Mills</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2013/02/what-you-see-are-the-three-speciality-tacos-from/">Tako Cheena</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pom Pom&#8217;s Tea House</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/08/pom-pom-is-one-of-those-places-that-weve-been-to/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 18:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pom Pom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tea]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/08/pom-pom-is-one-of-those-places-that-weve-been-to/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Pom Pom is one of those places that we’ve been to a half a dozen times since it last appeared on the blog. As we’ve said before, the food is delicious. You can’t go wrong with any of the sandwiches on the extensive menu. On this particular trip I ordered The Cobb – turkey, melted [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/08/pom-pom-is-one-of-those-places-that-weve-been-to/">Pom Pom&#8217;s Tea House</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/08/pom-pom-is-one-of-those-places-that-weve-been-to/attachment/410/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/tumblr_m855w7oQv81r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>Pom Pom is one of those places that we’ve been to a half a dozen times since it <a href="/tagged/Pom-Pom" target="_blank" rel="noopener">last appeared</a> on the blog. As we’ve said before, the food is delicious. You can’t go wrong with any of the sandwiches on the <a href="http://pompomsteahouse.com/our-menu" target="_blank" rel="noopener">extensive menu</a>.</p>
<p>On this particular trip I ordered The Cobb – turkey, melted blue cheese, tomato, watercress, red onion, bacon, and avocado. As I’ve said before, you either like blue cheese or you don’t, and I do. In fact, I would have been happy if there was a smidge more blue cheese, but as it was served it was very good. Sitting in front is a side of warm potato salad.</p>
<p>You can’t go wrong with Pom Pom’s Teahouse. The place is delicious.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/08/pom-pom-is-one-of-those-places-that-weve-been-to/">Pom Pom&#8217;s Tea House</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tako Cheena</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/05/today-is-the-start-of-taco-week-here-at-chow-down/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 20:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pom Pom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[taco week]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tacos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tako Cheena]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/05/today-is-the-start-of-taco-week-here-at-chow-down/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Today is the start of Taco Week here at Chow Down Orlando! This is the first of three taco centric reviews coming over the next few days. Don’t forget to submit your favorite taco places for us to check out in the future! It’s kind of hard to make out any unique features from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/05/today-is-the-start-of-taco-week-here-at-chow-down/">Tako Cheena</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/05/today-is-the-start-of-taco-week-here-at-chow-down/attachment/477/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/tumblr_m48cpxyFwF1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p><em>Today is the start of Taco Week here at Chow Down Orlando! This is the first of three taco centric reviews coming over the next few days. Don’t forget to <a href="/ask" target="_blank" rel="noopener">submit your favorite taco places</a> for us to check out in the future!</em></p>
<p>It’s kind of hard to make out any unique features from the five tacos, excuse me, <em>takos</em> pictured above with all the cilantro, onions, and cabbage lying about. But below all the green, purple and white lies the good stuff from Orlando’s newest taco house, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/pages/Tako-Cheena-by-Pom-Pom/174918999187662" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tako Cheena</a>.</p>
<p>Tako Cheena opened a few months back and is run by the fine folks from Pom Pom’s Tea House. They offer a number of unique taco options for all different taste preferences. Carla and I decided to sample five of the seven taco options. From the “House Tako” menu we sampled Thai Peanut Chicken, Indian Yellow Curry with Crispy Tofu, and Asian Braised Beef. From the “Specialty Tako” menu we went with Panko Crusted Cod and Chinese BBQ Char Siu Pork Belly.</p>
<p>I’ll be blunt, skip the House Tako’s all together and stick with the Specialties. The house options aren’t bad, they just don’t leave much of an impact nor carry much in the way of flavor. On the other hand, the Specialty Takos, especially the Panko Crusted Cod, take tacos to a whole other level. Specifically, the Panko Crusted Cod is one of the best taco options in Orlando. The flavors mixed with the crispy fish makes for a very enjoyable experience. So good, I had to order a second.</p>
<p>You can find Tako Cheena by Pom Pom at 932 Mills Ave.</p>
<p><em>Check back into Taco Week on Wednesday when we look at tacos from a place you might not expect.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/05/today-is-the-start-of-taco-week-here-at-chow-down/">Tako Cheena</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pom Pom&#8217;s Teahouse and Sandwicheria</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/pom-poms-teahouse-sandwicheria/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 23:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pom Pom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sandwich]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tea]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/pom-poms-teahouse-sandwicheria/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Considering I don’t drink tea, it may come across as a surprise that I’m a fan of two of Orlando’s teahouses – Infusion in College Park and Pom Pom’s on Bumby. Carla’s a fan of the tea at these places, but I’m a fan of the food. What you see there is the Fu Man [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/pom-poms-teahouse-sandwicheria/">Pom Pom&#8217;s Teahouse and Sandwicheria</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Considering I don’t drink tea, it may come across as a surprise that I’m a fan of two of Orlando’s teahouses – Infusion in College Park and Pom Pom’s on Bumby. Carla’s a fan of the tea at these places, but I’m a fan of the food.</p>
<p><img src="http://dl.dropbox.com/u/482444/Chow%20Down%20Orlando/pompom.jpg" alt="Pom Pom's" width="518.4" height="387.2" align="middle" /></p>
<p>What you see there is the Fu Man Chu, which is Asian pulled pork, watercress, goat cheese, ginger cranberry chutney, and red onions. It’s pretty difficult to put into words what stands out about this particular sandwich because of how great it all works together. It’s creamy and sweet and so very good.</p>
<p>In the background you can see Mama Ling Ling’s Thanksgiving Dinner which is everything you ever wanted in a Thanksgiving dinner, but in sandwich form: turkey, gouda, ginger cranberry chutney, stuffing, mashed potatoes, cream cheese and a side of gravy for dipping! Eating this sandwich I kind of know how Eve felt eating that apple.</p>
<p>On top of the delicious food, the atmosphere is a lot of fun, the staff is very friendly and there’s cool local art on the walls. It’s worth checking out.</p>
<p>Pom Pom’s Teahouse &amp; Sandwicheria is on Bumby between Washington and Central.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/pom-poms-teahouse-sandwicheria/">Pom Pom&#8217;s Teahouse and Sandwicheria</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
