<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Buca di Beppo &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/buca-di-beppo/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Buca di Beppo &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Buca di Beppo</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/buca-di-beppo/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 19:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buca di Beppo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/buca-di-beppo/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The other day some good friends of ours got married (congratulations you guys!) and we were invited to their rehearsal dinner at Buca di Beppo in Maitland. We had no idea we were going to be in for such a treat. After what we learned was the appetizer was served, we found out that this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/buca-di-beppo/">Buca di Beppo</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The other day some good friends of ours got married (congratulations you guys!) and we were invited to their rehearsal dinner at Buca di Beppo in Maitland. We had no idea we were going to be in for such a treat. After what we learned was the appetizer was served, we found out that this meal would span five glorious courses over about two solid hours. Since we didn&rsquo;t want to be rude and take pictures of our food in the middle of a rehearsal dinner, you&rsquo;ll have to deal with our descriptions.</p>
<p><strong>First Course &#8211; Antipasti and Pizza<br /></strong>The night began with a nice caprese salad: nice and ripe tomato slices with thick, fresh mozzarella drizzled with some olive oil. Nice and light and a great way to start. Paired with the caprese was a Margherita pizza &ndash; basically the exact same thing but in pizza form. Also very good.</p>
<p><strong>Second Course &#8211; Salad<br /></strong>We had a Caesar and a mixed green salad. What can you really say about salad?</p>
<p><strong>Third Course &#8211; Pasta<br /></strong>This course brought two amazing options: Penne Basilica and Ravioli al Pomodoro. The penne, covered with chopped broccoli and a cream sauce, was very rich and very good. However the ravioli stole the show. The massive mixture of cheeses (listed on the website as mozzarella, provolone, ricotta, and parmesan) make each bite nice and rich and very delicious. This might have been my favorite dish of the night.</p>
<p><strong>Fourth Course &#8211; Entrée<br /></strong>For the main course, we had both chicken and eggplant parmesan as well as green beans and broccoli. The chicken parm was delicious; crispy with a nice bite from the sauce and richness from the cheese. The eggplant parm was basically the exact same thing, just with eggplant instead of chicken. The only thing we wished was that the eggplant was cut a little thicker. The green beans were nice, although a little oily and the broccoli was dusted with parmesan cheese and cooked in garlic. They were pretty good.</p>
<p><strong>Fifth Course &#8211; Dessert<br /></strong>By the time dessert was served, we were almost fully in our food comas. However when the &ldquo;Double Dark Chocolate Cake&rdquo; arrived, our interest was re-piqued. Rich, but not too rich, the chocolate cake was very good. The cake was served with a giant (and when I say giant I mean seriously huge) bowl of tiramisu. I&rsquo;m not a huge coffee fan, but I figured I had tried everything else on the table thus far so I might as well try the tiramisu as well. It was good, and not too espresso-like, but after the giant slice of cake I only managed a few bites of tiramisu.</p>
<p>Since everything at Buca di Beppo is served family style, our table ended up with a lot of left overs. A whole lot of left overs. Enough, in fact, to produce two more full meals at home. And I&rsquo;m eating the final piece of chocolate cake once I finish writing this post. Everything about our Buca di Beppo was wonderful. And since it was the rehearsal dinner for our friend&rsquo;s wedding, it was even more special.</p>
<p>Buca di Beppo is in Maitland on 17-92 right across from the Enzian Theater.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/buca-di-beppo/">Buca di Beppo</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
