<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lido&#8217;s &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/lidos/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Lido&#8217;s &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Lido&#8217;s Italian</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 18:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido's]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>I must drive by Lido’s Italian half a dozen times a week. It’s located right at Orange and Michigan next to Play it Again Sports, and if you weren’t looking for it you’d never know it was there. But Lido’s is an Orlando staple and has seemingly been where it is forever. We went for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/">Lido&#8217;s Italian</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/attachment/435/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m5b1gwPNxn1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/attachment/436/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m5b1gwPNxn1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>I must drive by Lido’s Italian half a dozen times a week. It’s located right at Orange and Michigan next to Play it Again Sports, and if you weren’t looking for it you’d never know it was there. But Lido’s is an Orlando staple and has seemingly been where it is forever.</p>
<p>We went for dinner and the dining room was small, but filled with what seem to be regulars. An older couple a table over even ordered “the usual, but with meatballs.” I can see why people come back. The wait staff is friendly, more in line with your neighborhood diner, are address you as “deer.” This is a trait lost on a lot of waitresses these days.</p>
<p>The menu is simple – it’s your basic Italian menu but one block in the center of the menu caught my eye. The Pizzaoli is a unique dish that is listed as Lido’s best seller so I figured I’d give it a shot. It’s two chicken cutlets (unless you get the “large” plate which is three) with a layer of roasted red peppers, another layer of mozzarella, a pepperoni or two, and Lido’s marinara sauce served with a side of angel hair. The dish is delicious. All those flavors work really well together, and the roasted red peppers were a wonderful surprise on my first bite.</p>
<p>Carla ordered the tri-colored tortellini in a “pink” Alfredo sauce and asked to add mushrooms. The plate that arrived could have fed both of us, it was so large. The sauce was absolutely amazing and surprisingly thick. Needless to say, a box was definitely requested.</p>
<p>Lido’s also adds endless salad and breadsticks, a la Olive Garden, to their entrees. But unlike Olive Garden, their salad dressing tastes fresh and homemade, the croutons are obviously yesterdays breadsticks (which is awesome), and the breadsticks are giant, twisted monsters that just beg to be dipped in the sauce of whatever is on your plate.</p>
<p>Overall, Lido’s was a wonderful surprise. It’s not fancy, it’s not over complicated, but it’s good food with friendly service. Don’t waste your time looking for a website, because you won’t find one. But next time your on Michigan, right at the corner with Orange, take a look and you’ll see it. It’s next to Play it Again Sports and directly across the street from Arby’s. Parking is in the rear.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/i-must-drive-by-lidos-italian-half-a-dozen-times/">Lido&#8217;s Italian</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
