<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hard Rock &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/hard-rock/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Hard Rock &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Kitchen at the Hard Rock Hotel</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/one-of-orlandos-best-kept-secrets-is-the-kitchen/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 23:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burgers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hard Rock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Kitchen]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/one-of-orlandos-best-kept-secrets-is-the-kitchen/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>One of Orlando’s best kept secrets is The Kitchen at the Hard Rock Hotel. There are a few barriers that would keep people from being able to find The Kitchen, namely the fact that it’s in the Hard Rock Hotel at Universal. Another is the $25 self parking fee which is luckily validated if you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/one-of-orlandos-best-kept-secrets-is-the-kitchen/">The Kitchen at the Hard Rock Hotel</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/one-of-orlandos-best-kept-secrets-is-the-kitchen/attachment/656/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/tumblr_lsijrnRGfK1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/one-of-orlandos-best-kept-secrets-is-the-kitchen/attachment/657/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/tumblr_lsijrnRGfK1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>One of Orlando’s best kept secrets is The Kitchen at the Hard Rock Hotel. There are a few barriers that would keep people from being able to find The Kitchen, namely the fact that it’s in the Hard Rock Hotel at Universal. Another is the $25 self parking fee which is luckily validated if you spend at least $25 in the restaurant. Finally, finding it in the hotel itself isn’t exactly easy, as it’s basically in the basement. But if you can finally find The Kitchen, you’re in for a treat, well, for the most part.</p>
<p>I say for the most part, because there are some negatives that can’t really be avoided. Namely, because it’s in the Hard Rock Hotel, you’re surrounded by tourists on vacation whose kids don’t seem to have a volume button. It’s loud. The other downside is the fact that there’s often “character dining.” I say often because it’s basically every time I’ve been there. What this means is that about every 45 minutes or so, Homer Simpson (why him I have no idea) comes by your table to say hello and interrupt your meal weather you want him to or not. But you have to look past all this, because the food is very good.</p>
<p>Every time I’ve been to The Kitchen I’ve started the meal with the Crispy Calamari, pictured above. It’s fried in a light and very crispy batter and served with a delicious Thai chili sauce. It’s similar to the sauce Dexter’s serves with their potato chips. While it’s not the best Calamari I’ve had in town, Thai chili sauce can make anything amazing.</p>
<p>The Kitchen is named because it’s supposed to be the that fulfillment of childhood comfort food served from your home kitchen. So there’s meatloaf, mac and cheese, and other similar favorites along side higher end seafood, steak and chef’s specials. Feeling the comfort food bug, Carla ordered the chicken pot pie. At least she attempted to. The waiter wouldn’t accept her order, saying “wrong choice, everything on the menu is good except for the pot pie. You don’t want to go there.” I’ve never had a waiter be this honest before, but appreciated his honesty. Carla instead ordered a margherita flatbread and was thoroughly pleased with the result.</p>
<p>Typically I order the chef’s special of the night and am not disappointed. The night that we went, the chef’s special was a pan cooked chicken with blue cheese mash and corn fritters. Everything about that sounded delicious, but I was in the mood for a good, juicy burger. So I decided to try the signature “Kitchen Burger.” It’s advertised as a 10 oz certified angus beef burger and is topped with bacon, cheddar, lettuce, tomato, a delicious aioli and a horseradish sauce. All of this was placed on a warm, slightly buttered bun. This burger was one of the best ones I’ve had in a while. It was perfectly cooked, extremely juicy, and very good. The icing on the cake came in the form of a deep fried pickle in the middle of the plate.</p>
<p>On top of warning us about the pot pie, our waiter was very good and very attentive in the crowded restaurant. In fact, once he found out we were locals, he took 10% off our bill which was nice of him. All in all, if you can put up with the issues that The Kitchen has, it’s worth the experience. And be sure to spend some time wondering through the first floor of the hotel. Being that it’s the Hard Rock Hotel, there’s a lot of really cool music memorabilia all over the walls.</p>
<p>The Kitchen is in the basement of the Hard Rock Hotel at Universal Orlando.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/10/one-of-orlandos-best-kept-secrets-is-the-kitchen/">The Kitchen at the Hard Rock Hotel</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
