<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Dexter&#8217;s &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/dexters/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Dexter&#8217;s &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dexter’s in Thorton Park</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/the-other-night-we-tried-out-dexters-in-thorton/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dexter's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fish]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/the-other-night-we-tried-out-dexters-in-thorton/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The other night we tried out Dexter’s in Thorton Park. We’d never been there before, but our friends had and suggested that we order the homemade chip appetizer. I’m a sucker for homemade chips, so we of course agreed. They were good, though I didn’t notice there were both regular and sweet potato chips until [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/the-other-night-we-tried-out-dexters-in-thorton/">Dexter’s in Thorton Park</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/the-other-night-we-tried-out-dexters-in-thorton/attachment/677/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/tumblr_lrc6e3iaaP1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>The other night we tried out Dexter’s in Thorton Park. We’d never been there before, but our friends had and suggested that we order the homemade chip appetizer. I’m a sucker for homemade chips, so we of course agreed. They were good, though I didn’t notice there were both regular and sweet potato chips until it was pointed out to me. The chips, however, did come with a delicious sweet chili dipping sauce that was very good.</p>
<p>The sandwich I had was a piece of grilled mahi with all the toppings including onion rings all on a pretzel roll. While the fish itself wasn’t anything to write home about, the whole package was very good, especially with the little bite of salt from the pretzel bread. The sandwich was served with a little salad which was a nice alternative to fries.</p>
<p>While Dexter’s is kind of tucked away in Thorton Park, the acoustics of the place take away slightly from the charm. To say it was loud would be an understatement. Noise bounced all over the high concrete walls. All in all the food was good but the atmosphere was lacking. However when it comes to sharing a meal with old friends that you haven’t seen in awhile, it doesn’t really matter where you are, it’s always going to be a good experience.</p>
<p>Dexter’s can be found in Thorton Park in Downtown Orlando or in Winter Park just off Park Avenue.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/09/the-other-night-we-tried-out-dexters-in-thorton/">Dexter’s in Thorton Park</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
