<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Asian &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/asian/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<description>Exploring all that Orlando has to offer.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 20:05:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/cropped-IMG_0842-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Asian &#8211; Chow Down Orlando</title>
	<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hawkers</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/hawkers-is-one-of-my-favorite-places-in-town-i/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 18:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hawkers]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/hawkers-is-one-of-my-favorite-places-in-town-i/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Hawkers is one of my favorite places in town (I know you hear that a lot, but it’s true). Hawkers is based around the idea of street fare “hawked” on the streets in Asian countries. I call it Asian style-tapas. And it’s fantastic. The best way to enjoy Hawkers is with a group of friends [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/hawkers-is-one-of-my-favorite-places-in-town-i/">Hawkers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/hawkers-is-one-of-my-favorite-places-in-town-i/duck-tacos/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m48diwdm5l1r1ujdyo4_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/hawkers-is-one-of-my-favorite-places-in-town-i/hawkers-delight/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m48diwdm5l1r1ujdyo5_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/hawkers-is-one-of-my-favorite-places-in-town-i/tempura-green-beans/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m48diwdm5l1r1ujdyo3_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/hawkers-is-one-of-my-favorite-places-in-town-i/bean-sprouts/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m48diwdm5l1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/hawkers-is-one-of-my-favorite-places-in-town-i/chicken-skewer/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/tumblr_m48diwdm5l1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p><a href="http://www.facebook.com/hawkersstreetfare" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hawkers</a> is one of my favorite places in town (I know you hear that a lot, but it’s true). Hawkers is based around the idea of street fare “hawked” on the streets in Asian countries. I call it Asian style-tapas. And it’s fantastic.</p>
<p>The best way to enjoy Hawkers is with a group of friends who like to share. Order a bunch of stuff, and start the passing around. Sure, there will be a dozen small plates on your table, but it will be totally worth it.</p>
<p>Pictured above are, in order of how amazing I think they are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Duck Tacos which are just incredible. This is a must have for me every time we go.</li>
<li>Hawkers Delight which is a vegetarian dish. I actually chose to have the tofu left out, and ordered the five-spice fried tofu and added it to this dish. It’s a nice flavor and texture combination.</li>
<li>Tempura Green Beans. Anything that is battered and fried is instantly better than the regular version.</li>
<li>Bean Sprouts, which is light appetizer.</li>
<li>Chicken Skewer.</li>
</ul>
<p>Pretty much everything at Hawkers can be shared, with the exception of the soup bowls (unless you don’t mind eating out of the same bowl). But make sure you come hungry because, if you’re anything like me you’ll want to order half the menu. And it will be worth it.</p>
<p>Hawkers can be found on Mills.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/06/hawkers-is-one-of-my-favorite-places-in-town-i/">Hawkers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eclectic Kitchen</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/04/my-first-experience-with-eclectic-kitchen-was/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 20:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eclectic Kitchen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[food trucks]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/04/my-first-experience-with-eclectic-kitchen-was/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>My first experience with Eclectic Kitchen was highly anticipated. I’m a fan of all the Asian food verities and Eclectic Kitchen is Thai inspired. Everything on the menu sounded great; there were curry dishes, all kinds of good stuff. I decided upon the Chicken Basel Stir Fry, pictured above. The stir fry is what you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/04/my-first-experience-with-eclectic-kitchen-was/">Eclectic Kitchen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/04/my-first-experience-with-eclectic-kitchen-was/attachment/494/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/04/my-first-experience-with-eclectic-kitchen-was/attachment/495/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" srcset="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg 250w, http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo2_1280-500x500.jpg 500w, http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo2_1280-768x768.jpg 768w, http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo2_1280-830x830.jpg 830w, http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo2_1280-230x230.jpg 230w, http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo2_1280-350x350.jpg 350w, http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo2_1280-480x480.jpg 480w, http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/tumblr_m22ndpB8K61r1ujdyo2_1280.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 250px) 100vw, 250px" /></a>

<p>My first experience with Eclectic Kitchen was highly anticipated. I’m a fan of all the Asian food verities and Eclectic Kitchen is Thai inspired. Everything on the menu sounded great; there were curry dishes, all kinds of good stuff. I decided upon the Chicken Basel Stir Fry, pictured above.</p>
<p>The stir fry is what you would expect: quality flavors, nice rice. But the kicker is the over easy egg on top of the bowl. It’s not something I’m used to, though Carla would probably be ok with over easy eggs on every meal she eats. The egg white add a nice texture to the stir fry while the gooey yoke combines well with the sauce. It makes for a nice dish. The portion size isn’t wonderful, but ultimately nice for a lunch meal.</p>
<p>Also pictured is what was listed as dessert: Krispy Kreme bread pudding with a raspberry jam. Every since 4Rivers introduced me to Krispy Kreme bread pudding, I’ve been hooked. Eclectic Kitchen takes it a nice step forward with the raspberry jam. It’s sweet but not too sweet and makes for a nice treat.</p>
<p>Overall, the prices and portions of Eclectic Kitchen are good, the flavors are great, and it’s a nice addition to the Orlando food truck scene.</p>
<p>You can find <a href="http://twitter.com/t_eclectic" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Eclectic Kitchen on Twitter</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/04/my-first-experience-with-eclectic-kitchen-was/">Eclectic Kitchen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shin Shushi</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 21:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sushi]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>A few weeks ago Carla and I were looking for a nice place to eat before going to see Les Miserables at the Bob Carr. We put the question out on Twitter and received recommendations from fellow local bloggers Droolius and Eat Local Orlando. We took Droolius’ recommendation for Shin Shushi on North Orange Ave. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/">Shin Shushi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/attachment/544/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/tumblr_ly6bv5mL8a1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/attachment/545/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/tumblr_ly6bv5mL8a1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/attachment/546/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/tumblr_ly6bv5mL8a1r1ujdyo3_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>A few weeks ago Carla and I were looking for a nice place to eat before going to see <em>Les Miserables</em> at the Bob Carr. We put the question out on Twitter and received recommendations from fellow local bloggers <a href="http://droolius.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Droolius</a> and <a href="http://www.eatlocalorlando.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Eat Local Orlando</a>. We took Droolius’ recommendation for <a href="http://www.shinsushi.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Shin Shushi</a> on North Orange Ave. We’re really glad we did!</p>
<p>We started off with Beef Kushi Katsu, which were small, panko battered beef and vegetable skewers. I don’t know if I’ve ever had breaded and deep fried beef before and I’m not really sure why that is because it’s delicious.</p>
<p>Typically Carla is into sashimi and was very tempted to go in that direction. However some of the speciality rolls caught our eye and we went in a different direction for dinner. For our main course, we split three sushi rolls:</p>
<ul>
<li>The Maine (top right roll in the picture): An entire lobster roll tempura fried with some other additions. It was really good and surprisingly light for how large it was.</li>
<li>Crunch California (middle roll in the picture): This was your basic California roll, but tempura battered and deep fried. I had to try it and was very happy I did. It was good, especially when dipped in spicy mayo.</li>
<li>Surf and Turf (bottom left roll in the picture): Tempura battered strip and asparagus inside the roll with seared NY strip steak and a wasabi mayo on top. To say this was one of the best pieces of sushi I’ve ever eaten would be pretty close to the truth. And the best part was Carla didn’t like the mayo on top, so it was all mine.</li>
</ul>
<p>For dessert, we tried the tempura fried cheesecake (who wouldn’t?). It was really good. Basically two entire slices of cheesecake battered and fried (notice a patter with our choices for the evening?) served with a nice ice cream. It was a nice ending to the meal.</p>
<p>We were really happy with Droolius’ recommendation and are now passing it on: If you’re looking for really good sushi, check out Shin on North Orange Ave.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2012/02/a-few-weeks-ago-carla-and-i-were-looking-for-a/">Shin Shushi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bento Cafe</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 23:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bento]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sushi]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Prior to a year or so ago I did everything I could to stay away from sushi. The idea of raw fish wrapped up with rice sounded absolutely unappealing to me. Then I was introduced to the fact that most sushi isn’t actually raw. And now I’m a huge fan. The reason for my sushi [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/">Bento Cafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/attachment/608/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/tumblr_lvt6lxY9Wk1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/attachment/609/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/12/tumblr_lvt6lxY9Wk1r1ujdyo2_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>Prior to a year or so ago I did everything I could to stay away from sushi. The idea of raw fish wrapped up with rice sounded absolutely unappealing to me. Then I was introduced to the fact that most sushi isn’t actually raw. And now I’m a huge fan.</p>
<p>The reason for my sushi conversion is Bento Cafe in Downtown Orlando. We’ve talked about Bento before, as it’s one of our favorite places to eat in all of Orlando. They have great boxes, but the other day our meal was all about the sushi.</p>
<p>On this trip I ordered my favorite roll on the menu, the Special Mexican (pictured in the foreground of the picture above). The Special Mexican is tempura shrimp, cream cheese, avocado, topped with ebi, eel sauce, and spicy mayo. The crunch from the shrimp mixed with the delicious spicy may make for a really good combination.</p>
<p>Usually I pair this with a Dragon roll, but thought to venture to the other side of the menu on this trip. The back side has all kinds of speciality rolls that, frankly, usually intimidate me. To join the Special Mexican, I added the Bali Hai Mango. This roll is also shrimp tempura, cream cheese, and eel but is instead topped with mango and coconut flakes and then drizzled with eel sauce. Where the Special Mexican has that slightly spicy, creamy flavor from the mayo, the Bali Hai has a sweet and rough texture from the mango and coconut. It was very good.</p>
<p>Also pictured is the sashimi bowl that Carla got. It’s pictured because it’s pretty, but like I said above, it’s all raw and I don’t do raw fish. She really likes it though.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.bentocafesushi.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bento Cafe</a> is located in The Plaza downtown on Orange Ave.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/12/prior-to-a-year-or-so-ago-i-did-everything-i-could/">Bento Cafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bento Cafe</title>
		<link>http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/08/last-night-i-didnt-have-time-to-go-home-from-work/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 17:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[justincox]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bento]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/08/last-night-i-didnt-have-time-to-go-home-from-work/</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Last night I didn’t have time to go home from work before needing to be back for a meeting so I opted for take-out. Luckily, I work in the heart of Downtown Orlando which affords me proximity to a lot of great food options. Since I needed something relatively quick and exceptionally delicious, I decided [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/08/last-night-i-didnt-have-time-to-go-home-from-work/">Bento Cafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<a href='http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/08/last-night-i-didnt-have-time-to-go-home-from-work/attachment/695/'><img width="250" height="250" src="http://chowdownorlando.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/tumblr_lqewv16KFl1r1ujdyo1_1280-250x250.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>Last night I didn’t have time to go home from work before needing to be back for a meeting so I opted for take-out. Luckily, I work in the heart of Downtown Orlando which affords me proximity to a lot of great food options. Since I needed something relatively quick and exceptionally delicious, I decided to order from <a href="http://www.bentocafeshshi.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Bento Cafe</a>.</p>
<p>Bento is one of my favorite places to eat in Orlando. It’s relatively inexpensive and just about everything on the menu is great, including the sushi menu. For this particular meal I went with the Pad Thai bento box. A bento box is a small box containing different compartments of food to make a meal. The boxes at Bento come with your entree choice, a ginger salad, sticky rice, noodles, a vegetable, and a small dessert. All total, it amounts to a ton of food and well worth the $8ish price tag.</p>
<p>I’m not entirely sure why I went with Pad Thai last night – honestly it might have been the first thing I noticed on the menu and since I was still at work I wasn’t exactly paying much attention – though over the last few years I’ve probably eaten most of the boxes on the menu. They’re all really good with the Katsu being my favorite. The Pad Thai is good, not too spicy, and with all the other stuff makes a nice meal. I seem to remember there being peanuts on it in the past, but then again I might be thinking of a different entree as well. There’s a lot of them!</p>
<p>Bento is in The Plaza building on Orange Avenue.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/2011/08/last-night-i-didnt-have-time-to-go-home-from-work/">Bento Cafe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://chowdownorlando.com/">Chow Down Orlando</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
